{
    "target_configs": {
        "player": {
            "name": [
                "player_16_5SX2AE",
                "player_4_5SX2AE",
                "player_15_5SX2AE",
                "player_1_5SX2AE",
                "player_5_5SX2AE",
                "player_3_5SX2AE"
            ],
            "app_id": [
                16,
                4,
                15,
                1,
                5,
                3
            ],
            "animation": [
                "crouch",
                "crouch",
                "pick_up",
                "crouch",
                "pick_up",
                "stand"
            ],
            "feature_caption": [
                "A man with dark skin, wearing a black fedora, black turtleneck, black pants, and black shoes.",
                "A woman with fair skin, wearing a white and blue shirt, blue pants, dark boots, a gray bandana, and a utility belt with pouches",
                "A bald man with medium skin, wearing a brown turtleneck, dark pants, and brown shoes.",
                "A man wearing sunglasses, dark green long-sleeve shirt, light cargo pants, black gloves, and brown boots",
                "A female soldier wearing green tactical uniform, backpack, and black boots. Hair is tied back. She carries a utility vest and accessories.",
                "A woman with medium skin, dark hair in a bun, wearing a dark V-neck shirt, light pants, and brown boots"
            ],
            "start_pos": [
                [
                    -12338.524,
                    3164.694,
                    199.974,
                    0,
                    17.894967888113626,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    -12137.075,
                    3422.269,
                    200.086,
                    0,
                    -96.35765505612635,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    -12400.748,
                    3596.786,
                    200.086,
                    0.0,
                    -90.0,
                    0.0
                ],
                [
                    -12407.964,
                    3910.089,
                    199.88,
                    0,
                    -19.478831369864565,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    -12395.84,
                    2835.534,
                    200.086,
                    0.0,
                    -90.0,
                    0.0
                ],
                [
                    -12449.727,
                    4075.52,
                    199.059,
                    0,
                    97.2457087486772,
                    0
                ]
            ],
            "type": [
                "None",
                "None",
                "None",
                "None",
                "None",
                "None"
            ]
        }
    },
    "sample_configs": {
        "sample_center": [
            -12594.452,
            3514.685,
            199.92
        ],
        "sample_radius": 907.5965075846541
    },
    "refer_agents_category": [
        "player"
    ],
    "safe_start": [
        [
            -12976.025,
            2808.422,
            199.843,
            0,
            48.10933852346793,
            0
        ],
        [
            -12529.678,
            4607.997,
            199.059,
            0,
            -81.03342348174029,
            0
        ],
        [
            -11446.331,
            2996.234,
            218.153,
            0,
            150.95616532991366,
            0
        ]
    ],
    "Questions": {
        "relative_distance": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_fedora_hat, the_woman_in_floral_shirt or the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_floral_shirt",
                    "B. the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_floral_shirt"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_fedora_hat, the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants or the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants",
                    "B. the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_fedora_hat, the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses or the_woman_in_deep_V_top?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses",
                    "B. the_woman_in_deep_V_top"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_floral_shirt, the_man_in_fedora_hat or the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_fedora_hat",
                    "B. the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_man_in_fedora_hat"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_floral_shirt, the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants or the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants",
                    "B. the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_floral_shirt, the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses or the_woman_in_deep_V_top?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses",
                    "B. the_woman_in_deep_V_top"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants, the_woman_in_floral_shirt or the_man_in_fedora_hat?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_floral_shirt",
                    "B. the_man_in_fedora_hat"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_floral_shirt"
            },
            "Question 8": {
                "question": "Which is farther from the woman in camel vest, the_woman_in_deep_V_top or the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_deep_V_top",
                    "B. the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_deep_V_top"
            }
        },
        "counting": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "How many humans are in a crouch position in the scene?",
                "answer": "three"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "How many individuals are picking up objects?",
                "answer": "two"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "How many women are present in the scene?",
                "answer": "three"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "How many people have a bald head?",
                "answer": "one"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "How many men in the scene are not wearing glasses?",
                "answer": "two"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "How many individuals with light skin color are women?",
                "answer": "three"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "How many humans are standing in the scene?",
                "answer": "one"
            },
            "Question 8": {
                "question": "How many people are neither bald nor wearing glasses?",
                "answer": "four"
            }
        },
        "state": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "What's the state of the man in the fedora hat?",
                "options": [
                    "A. crouch",
                    "B. standing",
                    "C. sitting",
                    "D. walking"
                ],
                "answer": "A. crouch"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "What's the state of the woman in the floral shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. crouch",
                    "B. standing",
                    "C. picking up",
                    "D. running"
                ],
                "answer": "A. crouch"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "What's the state of the bald man?",
                "options": [
                    "A. holding something",
                    "B. standing",
                    "C. crouch",
                    "D. sitting"
                ],
                "answer": "A. holding something"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "What's the state of the man in light pants and sunglasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. crouch",
                    "B. standing",
                    "C. walking",
                    "D. picking up"
                ],
                "answer": "A. crouch"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "What's the state of the woman in the camo vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. holding something",
                    "B. standing",
                    "C. crouch",
                    "D. sitting"
                ],
                "answer": "A. holding something"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "What's the state of the woman in the deep V-top?",
                "options": [
                    "A. standing",
                    "B. crouch",
                    "C. sitting",
                    "D. holding something"
                ],
                "answer": "A. standing"
            }
        },
        "relative_location": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in floral shirt relative to the man in fedora hat?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the back-left of",
                    "B. To the front-right of",
                    "C. Behind",
                    "D. To the left of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. To the front-right of"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Where is the man in fedora hat relative to the woman in floral shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the back-left of",
                    "B. In front of",
                    "C. To the right of",
                    "D. Behind"
                ],
                "answer": "A. To the back-left of"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Where is the man in fedora hat relative to the bald man in brown sweater and black pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the left of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. In front of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "C. In front of"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Where is the bald man in brown sweater and black pants relative to the man in light pants and sunglasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the left of",
                    "B. In front of",
                    "C. Behind",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "A. To the left of"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Where is the man in fedora hat relative to the woman in camo vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. To the right of",
                    "C. Behind",
                    "D. To the left of"
                ],
                "answer": "C. Behind"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Where is the man in light pants and sunglasses relative to the woman in deep V top?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the right of",
                    "B. To the left of",
                    "C. Behind",
                    "D. In front of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. To the left of"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "Where is the bald man in brown sweater and black pants relative to the man in fedora hat?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front-right of",
                    "B. To the right of",
                    "C. Behind",
                    "D. To the left of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. To the right of"
            },
            "Question 8": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in deep V top relative to the bald man in brown sweater and black pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. To the left of",
                    "C. To the right of",
                    "D. Behind"
                ],
                "answer": "D. Behind"
            }
        }
    }
}